https://www.acuatlanta.net/privacy-policy-page-9.html

CART 0 ITEMS
Your Shopping Cart is empty!
Tiger Balm
Tishcon Corp.
Supplements
AdaptogensAmino AcidsDiet & Weight LossEnergyFish Oil & OmegasHerbal SupplementsMushroomsProbioticsSportsVitaminsSEE ALL SUPPLEMENTS...
Beauty Personal Care
Aromatherapy & Essential OilsFirst AidFacial & Skin CareHair CareMassage & Carrier OilsBath & ShowerOral Care
Functional Foods
BarsMeal ReplacementGreens & SuperfoodsOlive Oil & Spices EtcProtein PowderSoupSugar ReplacementTeas & CoffeeWater Health
HELP
Need some help? If none of these options work for you then scroll down and check the links in our footer...
Effective on May 25, 2018
This privacy statement describes how Acupuncture Atlanta collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: www.acuatlanta.net. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.
What personal Information do you collect and how do you use it?
We collect the following personal information from you:
Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number.
As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.
We use this information to
Send you requested product or service information
Send product updates or warranty information
Respond to customer service requests
Administer your account
Send you a newsletter
Send you marketing communications
Personalize product recommendations and promotions based on your interests
Respond to your questions and concerns
Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
Conduct research and analysis
Fulfill your order
Send you an order confirmation.
Information Obtained from Third Parties
We obtain address information about you from third party sources, such as the US Postal Service, to verify your address so we can properly ship your order to you and to prevent fraud.
Information Sharing
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.
We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
We may also disclose your personal information:
as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
if Acupuncture Atlanta is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.
For example, AcuAtlanta.net utilizes PayPal as our primary payment portal. When you use PayPal to finalize and pay for your order, you provide your credit card number directly to PayPal. PayPal's privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal website.
Do I have a choice to Opt-Out of your Newsletter or emails?
You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at cs@acuatlanta.net
Do you install Cookies on my computer?
We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.
Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information
To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate you may login to your account information page to make changes or set your email contact preferences. Additionally you may contact us at cs@acuatlanta.net.
Is my Information Secure?
Acupuncture Atlanta utilizes technologies including Transport Layer Security (TLS) and database encryption to ensure the privacy of your personal information. When you make an online purchase, our advanced security technology uses strong secure protocols to send your personal data to us, making it practically impossible for someone to intercept and extract that data.
To further protect your information, we utilize state of the art back-end systems and restrict employee access to your information. While we are confident ordering online is safe and secure, if for any reason you cannot access the secure server or feel uncomfortable ordering online, please feel free to place your order with us by phone at 1-866-910-1567. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at cs@acuatlanta.net.
Notification of Privacy Statement Changes
We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
Contact Information
You can contact us by writing or email us at the address below.
Acupuncture Atlanta
455 E. Paces Ferry Rd. Suite 222
Atlanta, GA. 30305
Email: cs@acuatlanta.net
Phone: 1-866-910-1567
JOIN OUR LIST
Subscribe to our list to receive updates on new arrivals, special offers and other discounts.
My Account
Personal Information
Change Password
Address Book
Order History
Tracking Orders
Reorder
Gift Card Balance
Tracking OrdersAffliatesAffiliate Log In
Customer Service
Product Request
Contact Us
AccessibilityDoctor Trusted SupplementsHow to improve mail deliveryShipping and ReturnsAbout UsInternational CheckoutTerms of UsePrivacy PolicyFAQsReviews
Contact Info
Acupuncture Atlanta
404.233.5080
1.866.910.1567
cs@acuatlanta.net
455 E. Paces Ferry Road, NE
Suite 222
Atlanta, GA. 30305
Store Customer Support Hours:
Mon - Fri:  9:00 AM - 5:00 PM (EST)
Sat & Sun: Closed
EMAIL US
SEND
Copyright (©) 2010 - 2014 Acupuncture Atlanta, Georgia.
